Ankit Nandwani

💌 ankitnandwani@outlook.com 📞 +91 7838299293 💡 Bengaluru, India 🟮 nandwaniankit

in Linkedin M Medium 🖸 Github 🧎 www.ankitnandwani.com

Summary

Automation Expert with over 8 years of experience. Core strengths include Java, Rest Assured, Selenium, TestNG, BDD and Agile. Seeking a remote position with a fast paced software company.

Skills

Java • Rest Assured • TestNg • Selenium • BDD/Cucumber • SQL • AWS/Azure • CI/CD

Maven • Git • Agile • Kafka • Spring Boot • Snowflake

Work Experience

Oct 2021 - present **SDET II,** DP World □

• Owning the backend quality for Network Pricing Manager API - responsible for providing freight rates to various clients.

• Implemented highly scalable and robust backend API Automation framework with CI/CD integration in Azure.

Senior SDET, Persistent Systems 🗷

• Working on LogMeIn's backend infra, which supports it's various UI offerings.

• Heavily utilising AWS, Snowflake to build Big data for Business Intelligence.

Oct 2017 - Oct 2020 **QA Consultant,** Centric Consulting

• Integrated Suite with Sauce Labs for distributing tests on the cloud

• Experience in creating Docker Containers leveraging Linux Containers.

SDET, Fareportal □ Jun 2016 - Oct 2017

• Implement Behavior Driven Development framework from scratch.

• Run Compatibility Testing (cross Windows/ Mac and Android/ iOS platforms)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER IN TEST, United Health Group ☑ Apr 2015 - Jun 2016

• Implemented automation framework using WebDriver, JAVA, Grid, Maven

• Worked in a highly dynamic AGILE environment.

PROGRAMMER ANALYST, Aon Hewitt □

Jan 2013 - Apr 2015

Responsible for analysing, processing and cleaning data from various sources.

Education

Bachelor of Technology, Maharshi Dayanand University

Jul 2009 - Jun 2013

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

• Major in Information Technology

Certifications

Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 7 Programmer ☑

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate [7]